# John Rock

# Web Developer

Passionate Web Developer with 4+ years of professional experience in front-end development.

My goal is to be a part of a dynamic work environment where I can utilize my knowledge and skills to assist with the growth of the organization and myself.

(570) 507-4498 johnmrock.jr@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/john-rock johnrock.me

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Lead Developer | Net Driven

August 2019 - Present

- Accelerated development by creating a library of commonly used assets.
- Spearheaded project to implement the use of the CSS preprocessor SCSS on platform by using a Gulp.js workflow.
- Collaborate with the back end team to ensure product deployments are rolled out efficiently and accurately.
- Manage and train remote developers.
- Review and delegate daily tasks in the work queue.
- Create process documentation.
- Debug and deploy fixes for errors on the platform.
- Create custom reports using Salesforce to refine workflow.

## Front-End Developer | Net Driven

July 2016 - August 2019

- Develop websites on the DotNetNuke platform for the automotive industry.
- Work with HTML, CSS, and jQuery to convert wireframes into fully functioning websites.
- Manage all national tire rebates to ensure assets are created and rebates are set to start and expire on the correct date.
- Design graphics for websites using Adobe Creative Suite.

#### **EDUCATION**

### Keystone College | La Plume, PA

August 2014 - July 2016

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

## Johnson College of Technology | Scranton, PA

August 2012 - May 2014

Associate in Computer Information Technology

#### **SKILLS**

Project Management Research and Development Troubleshooting Employee Training

#### **LANGUAGES**

HTML

CSS / SCSS

JavaScript GraphQL jQuery Markdown MySQL PHP Node.js React

## **TOOLS**

DotNetNuke
Figma
GatsbyJs
G Suite
Git
Gulp.js
Jira
Netlify
REST API
Salesforce
Visual Studio Code
Wordpress

Adobe Creative Suite